http://azbiz.com/site/privacy_policy.html

Jobs
DONATE!
Jobs
DONATE!
This is the Privacy Policy for all Websites owned or operated by Tucson Local Media LLC, including, without limitation the Websites listed here (collectively, the "Site").TucsonLocalMedia.comTucsonWeekly.comInsideTucsonBusiness.comWe respect your privacy and appreciate the confidence you have placed in the Site. We are committed to protecting your privacy and preserving your trust. Please carefully review this Privacy Policy to learn about how we collect, use, and protect any personal information you provide us and your choices for managing your personal information.Managing Information PreferencesWe want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or if you wish to exclude your personal information from our direct marketing purposes, please feel free to contact us at:7225 N. Mona Lisa Rd. #125Tucson, AZ 85741(520) 797 4384E-mail: tucsonweekly@tucsonlocalmedia.comIf you would like to correct, update, or change your personal information with us please contact us the same way.What Types Of Information Do We Collect?We collect information that may personally identify you (such as your name, address, telephone number, email address, billing information, or other data which can be reasonably linked to such information) only if you choose to share such information with us. For example, we may collect personal information from you when you register on the Site, subscribe to one of our services, enter sweepstakes, contests or other promotions, and at other times. We also collect credit card information in connection with any purchase you make on or through the Site. The decision to provide this information is optional; however, if you decide not to register or provide such information, you may not be able to use certain features of the Site or other services.We may automatically collect non-personal information that does not identify an individual user, such as IP (internet protocol) address, ISP (internet service provider), the Web browser used to visit the Site, the time the Site is visited, which Web pages were visited on the Site, a unique mobile device identifier (in connection with the use of the Sites or related services from mobile devices) and other anonymous Site usage data.We also use cookies (a small file containing a string of characters that uniquely identifies your Web browser) and Web beacons (an electronic file placed within a Web site that monitors usage). We use cookies and Web beacons to improve the quality of the Site. Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your Web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, certain features of the Site may not work if you delete or disable cookies. Certain of our Service Providers may use cookies and Web beacons in connection with the services they perform on our behalf, including, without limitation, ad serving.How Do We Use The Information We Collect?We will not sell, share, or rent personal information to third parties, and we will not otherwise disclose personal information to third parties, without your permission, except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.We use personal information and non-personal information for internal purposes, including:* enhancing your experience at the Site;* performing administration and technical support for the Site;* enabling you to enter sweepstakes, contests and other promotions;* enabling you to use certain services and features available on or through the Site;* creating aggregate information about demographics and usage patterns;* inviting our promotional vendors and advertisers—with your permission—to call to your attention special offers, products and services that may be of interest to you; and* enabling purchases of goods and services.We may use aggregate information to measure general Site usage patterns and characteristics of our user base, and we may include such aggregate information about our audience in reports to our commercial vendors. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics (for example, a certain percentage of our users live in a certain area) without your permission in order to describe our audience to existing and prospective advertisers or other third parties. However, this aggregate information does not reference names, phone numbers, e-mail addresses, or other personal information, and it is not traceable to a specific recipient or user email address.We also may share personal information with entities controlling, controlled by, or under common control with Tucson Local Media. In the event that Tucson Local Media is merged, or in the event of a transfer of our assets, we may disclose or transfer your personal information and non-personal information in connection with such transaction.From time to time, we might establish a business relationship with other persons or entities whom we believe trustworthy and whom we have asked to confirm that their privacy practices are consistent with ours ("Service Providers"). For example, we may contract with Service Providers to provide certain services including credit card processing, advertising, promotions, analytics tools, data management, Web hosting, and Web development. We provide our Service Providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. Each Service Provider must agree to implement and maintain reasonable security procedures and practices appropriate to the nature of your information in order to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.We may work with third-party advertising companies which may use information about your visit to the Site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you on the Site and on third-party Web sites. From the Site, these companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or use other technologies such as Web beacons or pixel tags. Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party advertisement serving company may collect from you.Although unlikely, in certain instances we may disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe it is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who may be causing injury to you, to Tucson Local Media or its affiliates, or to others. We may also disclose your personal information when we believe the law or legal process requires such disclosure. Please note that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit your personal information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission.SecurityWe use encryption and authentication tools to protect the security of personal information that you share with us. However, no data transmission over the Internet (or, with respect to our mobile services, over cellular phone networks) can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect personal information, we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from the Site, and you do so at your own risk.Links To Third-Party Web SitesThe Site may contain links to Web sites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked Web sites may be different from our Privacy Policy. You access such linked Web sites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of a linked Web site before disclosing any personal information on such site.Discussion Board, Forums and Other User Generated ContentOur online chat and comment areas, bulletin boards, social networks, other public forums and user-generated content (i.e., photos, videos) can be a useful way for you to express yourself to other online users. When you post messages or otherwise use these features, the information that you provide (including personal information) may be publicly available to, collected by, and used by third parties. We are not responsible for the content of such messages or images posted by users or such disclosures of personal information.Children's Privacy StatementWe do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records.Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, e-mail addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We won’t knowingly allow anyone under 13 to register with us or to provide any other personal information. If you’re under 13, please do not provide us with any personal information about yourself (such as your name, your e-mail address or your phone number). SecurityThis site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.Email NoticesTucson Local Media sends a variety of emails to registered users who post listings. These emails include but are not limited to confirmations that a listing has been posted, notices that the listing is about to expire, and notices that the listing has been deleted by an administrator. These emails are a necessary feature for Tucson Local Media.Tucson Local Media also sends a variety of newsletter emails only to users who have subscribed to such services. When subscribing to a newsletter, user provided email addresses are used only for sending the newsletters and not distributed further. If you do not wish your email be included in the newsletter lists, please do not subscribe to our newsletters. You may unsubscribe at any time.Policy ChangesIf we decide to change our Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting the changed Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to abide by the Privacy Policy as changed. If you object to any such changes, your sole recourse shall be to cease using the Site.Effective Date: 3/12/2019If you have any questions, concerns or comments regarding our privacy policy, please send a detailed email totucsonweekly@tucsonlocalmedia.com and we will make sure to address your concerns.
Financial Fix by Vantage West
Different Names, Same Address: How Big Businesses Got Government Loans Meant for Small Businesses
ProPublica is a nonprofit newsroom that investigates abuses of power. Click here to read their biggest stories as soon as they’re published.
More Financial Fix
Latest News
Biosphere 2 study: Tropical forests may be more resilient to rising temperatures than predicted
Southern AZ COVID-19 AM Roundup for Thursday, Dec. 10: Nearly 5K new cases reported today; Death toll rises by 73; TMC nurses ask public to take more precautions; Record numbers of people visit ERs; Tucson under curfew
House calls: Arizona lawmakers land in COVID-19 quarantine more often
Pima County issues mass alert as COVID-19 cases surge
TMC nurses plead with the public as COVID-19 surges
What to know about open carry laws in Arizona
Southern AZ COVID-19 AM Roundup for Wednesday, Dec. 9: More than 4400 new cases; 108 eight new deaths; AZ cases top 382K; Tucson now under curfew
Holiday punch: COVID-19 worries mean no holiday party for most offices
Real Estate & Construction
Re-revitalizing Downtown: Executive Excellence winner Fletcher McCusker on the past - and future - of Tucson Business
You’d be hard-pressed to find an aspect of Tucson that entrepreneur Fletcher McCusker hasn’t influenced in some way. Whether it’s local restaurants, hotels, music, healthcare, business, education or radio, the University of Arizona alumnus has worked with all of them. It’s for this reason Mc…
More Real Estate & Construction
On the Menu
On the Menu: Whiskey Del Bac's Winter Release to be unveiled Saturday
If reassurance can be bottled, we can all take great comfort in the fact that Veronica Townsend has us covered.
More On the Menu
Business Chatter
Chamber Chatter: Election is over but work remains to be done
I’ll start with the good news: the 2020 election is over. The bad news: the politics of 2020…
Chamber Chatter: Supporting Tucson’s businesses
COVID-19 has created insurmountable obstacles that many businesses simply will not be able t…
UA Center for Innovation on the international stage
International efforts at Tech Parks Arizona are being recognized from multiple organizations…
Minority-owned business has a
big impact on our community
There are reports and statistics that inform and promote the value of minority-owned busines…
Arizona bars reopen amid COVID-19 guidelines
PHOENIX – As Arizona bars have reopened after months of being shut down during the COVID-19 …
© Copyright 2020 Inside Tucson Business, 7225 N. Mona Lisa Rd. #125 Tucson, AZ | Terms of Use | Privacy Policy
Powered by BLOX Content Management System from TownNews.com.
